

GitHub

@DmitryHordyna

Area

Ukraine,Kiev

 \boxtimes

Mail

hordynadmytro@gmail.com

C

Phone +38 093-758-75-49

TECH SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- GIT
- JavaScript
- React

SOFT SKILLS

- Adaptability
- Flexibility
- Teamwork
- Energy
- A sense of humor

SPOKEN LANGUAGES

- English B1
- Ukraine Native speaker
- Russian Advance

HOBBIES

Socialising with firends and family, playing football, reading books ,cycling bicycle,computing and also travaling.

Hordyna Dmytro

Full-Stack Developer

ABOUT ME

At the moment I am studying on the GoIT course, specializing in Full-Stack Developer. The training provides a lot of tech-skills practice, participation in team projects and IT English. At this stage, I am completing the Javascript and React course and now studying Node JS. Open to internships and vacancies for junior.

PROJECTS

Team project

| Team project Ice-cream[HTML5, CSS | 3] |
|--|-------|
| Team project Event Booster [HTML5, CSS: | 3,JS7 |

Self projects

| Web Studio | [HTML5, CSS3] |
|----------------------------|----------------|
| Barber Shop | [HTML5, CSS3] |
| The Founder | [JavaScript] |
| Country,LocalStorage,Timer | [JavaScript] |
| Filmoteka | [React] |
| Phonebook | [React] |

EDUCATION

National University of Life and Environmental Sciences of

Ukraine

Septermber 2013 - December 2018 Ukraine

Design engineer (Master)

GOIT School

Septermber 2020 - till now | Online

Full-Stack Developer

Rolling Scopes School

July 2021 - till now Online

Front-End Developer

Speak Up School

October 2020 - till now Online

Improving the level of English

WORK EXPERIENCE

Design engineer

June 2017 - December 2018 | Ukraine

Draw details car using Compas 3D and SolidWorks.

Monitoring and updating of documents.

Internship from the university agricultural practices

May 2019 - December 2021 Denmark